



### Key skills

- . HR Generalist Activities
- · Payroll Processing
- Assistant Manager HR
- Employee Engagement
- Employee Grievances
- HR Manager
- PMS
- · Learning And Development
- Training Need Analysis
- MIS
- Budgeting
- Management Information System
- HRIS
- Corporate HR
- HR Analytics



## **Personal Information**

City Navi

Mumbai

Country INDIA



#### Languages

- English
- Hindi
- Marathi

# Vaishali

Asst. Manager - HR & Admin.



(+91) 9769440418

vacchu2002@gmail.co



**Profile Summary** 

Human Resource Specialist offering a rich career span of 15+ years in the areas of Recruitment Selection, Training Development, Performance Management, Compensation Benefits, Payroll, Leave and Attendance Management, HR MIS, F F Settlement, IR, Statutory Compliance like EPF, ESI, PT, LWF, Bonus, Annual Returns, Contract license etc., General Administration.



#### Education

Ph.D/Doctorate, 2007

Welingkar University, Mumbai

**MBA/PGDM, 2013** 

Institute of Chartered Financial Analysts of India (ICFAI)

**B.Com, 2005** 

**Mumbai University** 



Work Experience

Apr 2018 - Present

Asst. Manager - HR & Admin.

Shubhada Polymers Products Pvt. Ltd.

Working as an Asst. Manager-HR, 11 years relevant exp.

Oct 2016 - Mar 2018

Senior HR Executive

Lift & Shift India Pvt. Ltd

Working as in Sr. HR Executive (Generalist) - Recruitment, Payroll, Employee Engagement, performance appraisal, statutory compliance etc..

Nov 2013 - Oct 2016

**HR Executive** 

Pace Business Machines Pvt. Ltd.



Certification

linkedin.com/in/vaishali-k-25372167